Motif
Popsicle
Dance Work
Involving All
The dance of instinct, the authenticity of proof
That's how you prove you exist.
Ladies awsze please
Seventeen.
Today we're shooting for colored contacts.
We're doing a cute summery shoot like this.
My eyebrows are big today, so I'm going to do my best to blur my eyes.
I'm looking forward to it!
It's the earth!
So cute!
Cute!
Cute.
Oh, there's an eyebrow.
There's the eyebrows.
Feels like I've been avoided.
Hi. - Hi.
I haven't been wearing colorful coast too much, but...
I'm thinking of using this as an opportunity to wear color contacts on a regular basis.
I haven't been able to find anything that suits me at all
I haven't bought any yet, but
I think I'm going to buy some.
Aren't these good?
Do you think they'll look good on me?
I guess so.
See you later.
Thank you for your hard work.
We'll be waiting for you.
It's been fun.
I'm going home.
Okay, let's go back. Over there.
I'm done.
Yay.
I made it a stylish and cute shoot.
I'm looking forward to it.
?
We're shooting color contacts.
I'm wearing contacts that show the rim of my black eyes a little more clearly.
The outfits are so cute!
I'm wearing tulle.
I'm wearing a white outfit.
It's so cute!
I'm wearing it on the egret.
We're going to have an ing shoot later, so I'm going to enjoy that as well.
Yeah. - Yeah.
What's the video?
It's a one-tube video.
Okay, well, you don't have to be so smart about it.
We're filming color contacts.
Can you see them? This one.
These contacts.
No, they're not! It's not my hand.
So, thank you very much.
You're too close.
I'm always told I'm too close.
Thank you very much.
You're higher.
Wait a minute.
You... I want some more.
That's good. You're so cute.
Good morning
Good morning.
I brought you my clothes.
Put them here.
Wow.
Here.
Mmm-hmm.
Here it is, just as it is, with water.
Good morning.
We are shooting a music video today
Mmm-hmm.
How many music videos have you shot this month?
Solo and Sakana?
Solo and Sacana... this month, I think.
Well, the whole month.
I've shot about a handful.
I'll do my best again today.
My Patronus is like...
She's like a girl with a ponytail.
I'm going to do my best today
I'm going to do my best today with my guardian spirit watching over me.
I've been able to squeeze in some weight
Catwalking's music video is a horror story
Various poltergeists happen in the low point camera
I hope to make a horror movie that is funny and cool.
I hope we can do it in a cool way while adding some funny elements to the horror.
It will be a poltergeist!
From now on
I'm going to be a poltergeist!
I think I was the most excited person during the music video shooting last year.
I'm not that good with scary things like ghosts.
but I love horror movies and stuff.
I'm really happy to be able to make this kind of music video.
I'm so excited!
It's finished!
It's amazing!
It's flying!
He's doing his neck like this.
I was thinking of doing it backwards.
It's coming in this way.
Oh, it's coming in this way.
It's hard to get a good shot.
Well, let's just do lunch.
Yes, please.
Q. What are your goals for the future?
Q. What is your future goal?
Ears.
I've been talking a lot.
At the moment, I've always been a zombie.
I'm in a state where I don't know who I am.
I hope to be myself again by the end.
Q. What are your future goals?
I'm supposed to be the one who says I hate cat ears the most on a daily basis.
But for some reason, I end up wearing cat ears pretty early in the game.
I don't know why.
I will do my best.
Q. What are your future goals?
I'm hoping to be able to wear cat ears even though all three of them are wearing them.
I am wondering why they decided not to have cat ears.
I'm wondering why.
Will I be rewarded?
Will it pay off?
Yes, I think so.
You just said...
I'm feeling very depressed.
Depression.
I don't think I'm there yet.
Thank you very much.
One more time One more time One more time
One more time, one more time
Let's try one more time.
If you don't laugh a little weird or something.
I can really fight.
All right, so take two.
I'll give you your take two.
Cut.
How was that?
Yes, cut.Yes, cut.
Okay. Okay.
Perfect.
Yes, cut.
Yes, OK
No, I don't want it. No, I don't want it.
The usual answer is...
Where are you doing it?
What a pain in the ass. What a pain in the ass.
And the pride of standing on your chest
And the way you look
I'm swaying, I'm swaying
I've been missing my toys
I'm sorry I didn't agree
Yeah, you must be tired of it
Come on, it's time to go.
I'll take the Dancing Club's bartery.
Please.
The Dancing Club's Vertary.
I'd like to go see it.
This is not the time to drop it. It's up to me. It's not a mistake that will come.
If you could see me not giving up.
I wonder if the dawn will clear
Let your heart echo
No time to drop it, it's not a mistake, it's up to you
Okay, we're cutting.
Let's go one more time.
Oh!
Racine.
It's only the first or second time.
I'll try my best.
Oh.
Oh, no.
Well done!
Thank you very much. Come again!
Glad to hear it. Come translate.
Yes, cut.
Yes, ok.
Pre-copinec appeared.
A little bit of chew.
A little bit of chew. Chewt hamburger chew.
What's wrong?
A little bit.
It's cute.
What was that?
Dancing around.
He's cute.
He's a good boy.
Oh, no.
He's cute.
Cute.
Spit up some blood. Spit up some blood.
Yes, cut.
Cut.
Cute.
I took it with one hand.
Hold the camera properly.
Oh, wow! That's great!
That's so cute.
I don't know what to do with this.
# I never made it to the stage #
# I dreamed I'd go on stage #
Yes, cut!
# I'll name you now
Okay!
# Future, future, future, future
# Let there be a voice in this world #
♪ I won't go in sideways ♪
We are about to break ground.
We are doing our best to shoot with the cat.
I'll do my best!
Yes, cut.
Here comes the cut.
Can I go one more time?
Cut.
Okay. - Okay.
Okay, thank you.
OK, so is that it?
Step.
Yes, OK
Yes, thank you
Yes, thank you.
Looking good.
Three seconds exactly.
That's funny.
I don't know, it's a little bit like...
Pose like a model.
Oh, that's good.
That's really well done.
You did it so well.
I'm serious. I'm serious.
What's this?
It's so cute.
Oh, my God.
Yes, thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Let's do a little double on this one.
Yes, it's cool.
Cool.
Yes, cut!
OK.
Okay, Ririka, that's it.
Thank you very much.
I wonder who the next before aster will be?
Luka Original!
Kankankan!
Please pose differently from Ririka-chan!
Bifo-ay-yan!
Oh, that's nice!
So cute!
Yes, katto!
Okay, okay!
Well, we're all done shooting here, Luka.
Enjoy!
Thank you very much!
Here's one for you!
Oh, nice!
Amazing!
That's good.
Okay, one more round
One more round.
Yes, sir.
Cut!
OK!
Thank you very much.
Yes!
Can I think about it on the water side?
Sure.
What? On your stomach?
I want you to catch it on the top.
I'm scared.
Okay, okay.
Cut!
With a cool smile at the end.
Nice!
Cut.
OK, it's perfect. Thank you.
That's it. We're done.
With the mashed art done.With the mashed art done.
I'm done!
I finished 3 of them today!
It was so much fun!
I don't even know what I'm shooting.
But it was fun.
I could really change the shots if I didn't have to laugh or do anything weird.